[music]
Hello.
[laughter]
police
sir. Super sir.
[laughter]
Sir,
Commissioner.
Okay. [laughter]
[laughter]
Sir,
sir.
Please sir.
Okay.
Thanks, sir.
>> [laughter]
>> Okay.
Okay. Okay. Thanks. Hey.
Yeah. foreign.
Yeah. Yeah.
Sir, come
sir. foreign.
[laughter]
Masterch.
forum.
What is it?
left.
forch.
Hello.
for
the
Huh?
[music]
Let's do it.
Yeah. daily.
Hey,ch.
for
I don't Speech. Speech. Speech.
>> [music]
>> India is my country. Our country is
India. All India is my brothers and
sister. India is big country.
[music]
You're lucky. Get
you done like that.
>> [music]
>> First
jumping.
[music]
Hello.
>> [music]
>> Hey,
hey,
hey.
foreign.
[laughter]
Give me my
>> [laughter]
>> drive. Hello.
for
sorry please. Sorry.
Please, let's go.
[music]
Secret.
foreign.
Hey
Excuse me. Hello, sir. Hello.
[screaming]
Wet than D.
>> [snorts]
>> Don't
forchech.
[gasps]
Okay.
[panting]
Where is it? Where is it?
>> [music]
[music]
[snorts]
>> Huh?
foreign
speech.
Foreign speech. Foreign speech.
for
[sighs]
currency.
[laughter]
Huh?
[screaming]
>> [laughter]
>> Boy,
drunk
boy.
set.
Huh? Huh?
Huh?